COSTA WAEZ: I was going to talk to you today about how we do maintenance.
Let's start with this hookah here.
Just to tell you, every time you're going to smoke hookah, you're going to change the water.
When you're going to clean the hookah after you finish smoking, you be careful when taking this one because this one preserves heat and make sure don't touch it and burn your hand.
Just move it carefully and place it in the sink or on some place that you don't burn anything, and take this one apart, you wash it.
And if you wash it in the dishwashing machine, that's fine if it's dishwashing machine safe.
And also, you can wash it with a hand, and you can soak it with hand, hot so--with hot water and soap, and the bottle, the same thing.
When you take it apart, make sure the pipe always will be dry.
Don't touch it with water and don't get it cleaned with anything.
This one will be soaked in the water.
The bottle, also, the same thing, water and soap, clean, dry, and be ready to use again.